wp-puzzle.com 2018-09-17

# Privacy policy while using WP Puzzle shop

_7 February, 2016_

Privacy policy, described below, applies to all information which site _wp-puzzle.com_ ( _“Site”_ ) may get about user during _Site_ use.

The main provisions of our privacy policy can be formulated as follows:

  * We do not share your personal information with third parties.
  * We do not share your contact information without your consent.
  * You assign volume of disclosed personal information by yourselves.

## Date collected

We collect  following information:

  * Personal information which User provide us by completing forms on our _Site._
  * Technical information automatically collected by the _Site_ software during its visit.

## Use of information

Information, you provide by completing forms on our _Site_ , may be used by us for:

  * _User_ identification registered on _Site_ ;
  * access to personalized _Site_ recourses;
  * establishment of _User_ feedback, including notifications, inquiries regarding use of _Site_ or Site products, processing of requests and applications from _User_ ;
  * notifications of _Site User_ about order status;
  * handling and receiving payments.

All contact information, you provide to us, is disclosed only with your permission. Email addresses are never published on Site and used by us only to contact you.

## Providing information to third parties

We never provide your personal information to third parties unless it can be required by legislation (for example, at the request of court).

## Use of cookies

User identification technology is used on _Site_ , based on the use of cookies. Cookies – are small text files that are stored on your computer by web browser.

While using _Site_ on computer by the _User_ , which is used for access by him, cookies can be recorded which later are used for automatic _User_ authorization on the _Site_ and for collection of statistic data about the _Site_ traffic in particular. We never store your personal data or passwords in cookies. If you are of opinion that for one reason or another use of cookies technology is unacceptable to you, you have a right to prohibit storing cookies on computer, used for access to _Site_ , by setting browser appropriately. However, you should bear in mind that all Internet services, used this technology, will be unavailable.

## Links to other sites

On this site you may be offered links to other sites. We do not accept any responsibility for liability in respect of your privacy on these websites. We strongly recommend that you read the privacy policy of each website that you access. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by the _Site_ _wp-puzzle.com_ _._

## Date security

_Site_ Administration protects the information provided by users, and uses it only in accordance with the Privacy Policy. We take all necessary and sufficient organizational and technical measures and precautions to protect the _confidentiality of personal data._

## Final provisions

None of statements contained here do not mean formation of contract or agreement between _the Site Owner_ and _the User_ , providing personal information. The Privacy policy will only inform you about _Site_ approaches to work with personal data. We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time without notice.

Contact

If you have any question, please [contact us](mailto:privacypolicy@wp-puzzle.com).
